

CONTACT



867-6899090



ankitspatel1990



ankitspatel1990@gmail.com



ankitpatel710.github.io

SUMMARY

Ankit is an IT Technician who want to expand his knowledge by choosing a path of Network Administrator. Ankit has terrific technical troubleshooting skills and good interpersonal skills to assist customers with computer issues. Ankit has bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering and one year of experience of IT Technician.

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- QUICK LEARNER
- **GOOD TEAM PLAYER**
- STRONG WORK ETHICS
- RESPONSIBLE, PUNCTUAL
- **GOOD PROBLEM SOLVING**

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Routing, Switching, IT Security, Troubleshooting

Strong Understanding of OSI Models, Protocols, IP

Solid Subnetting Skills

Static Routing and Dynamic Routing Protocols (RIP, EIGRP, BGP)

Switching (VLAN, inter VLAN Routing, Trunking, Switch Port Security)

Functional Understanding of ACL, DNS, DHCP, NAT

Troubleshooting Familiarity with Microsoft Operating System

Knowledge of Linux Operating System (Fedora, CentOS, Ubuntu)

Working knowledge of Virtualization, Data Storage

Tools: Cisco Packet Tracer, Wire Shark, Putty, Hyper-V, VMWare, VCenter Server, MacOS, Chrome OS, Remote Desktop Software

Other Software Development Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Databases

EDUCATION

SAIT, Calgary, AB

2019-2020

Network Technician, Certificate

Centennial, Toronto, ON

2013-2015

Software Engineering Technology, Diploma

Gujarat University, India

2008-2012

Computer Engineering, Bachelor's

EXPERIENCE

BISAG, Gujarat, India

2012-2013, IT Technician

Installed and Maintained Company's Computer Systems and Network

Perform Installation and Upgrades as Company's Requirement

Troubleshooting of systems on Site as well as offsite

Provide Technical Assistant to Customers over Telephone as needed

CERTIFICATE

AWS Masterclass

2019, stackskills

Web Developer Bootcamp

2019, udemy

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Pho Lien, Whitehorse, YT

2015-2019, Customer Service Representative/Server/Cashier

Walmart Canada, Whitehorse, YT

2015-2016, Stock Associate

La Sani Grill, Toronto, ON

2013-2015, Supervisor